I am Dr. Jordan P. Petersen.
Professor at the University of Toronto.
Clinical Psychologist.
Author of the best-selling book "12 Laws of Life"
Which has sold 12 million copies worldwide.
Translated into 50 languages.
And I gave live lectures about him in 150 cities across North America ...
Europe, Australia and New Zealand.
I also produced a series of popular podcasts.
Which will be included weekly ...
On the Westwood One Podcast every Sunday.
And I'm going to hang out with my daughter Mukalla Petersen.
If you want to understand yourself and other people much more deeply ...
And keep up with the latest scientific discoveries and philosophical ideas.
The podcasts of Jordan B. Petersen on "Westwood One" ...
It might be exactly what you are looking for.
It is an appeal to individual responsibility ...
Courage and truth in the face of life's difficulty and tragedies.
Listen and subscribe for free ... today.